Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records
1971-2016
1975-2009
Fales Library and Special Collections
New York Foundation for the Arts
MSS.515
96 linear feet in 96 record cartons
The New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA) was founded in 1971 in New York City by a group of artists who were part of the New York State Department of Cultural Affairs (NYSCA) to create an organization that would provide artists like themselves with resources guidance and funding for their art projects that NYSCA could not provide directly. NYFA grew over the decades to become one of the leading organizations providing grants and services in New York City, New York State, and in the country. NYFA's programs are dedicated to providing guidance and support for artists and smaller arts organizations seeking city, state, and federal organization funding. This collection documents NYFA's nearly 50 year history including individual artist and small arts organization grant recipient files with applications/project descriptions, agreements, project advice, panel critiques, promotional information, and artist work samples. This collection also includes founding documents, marketing material, financial and budgetary information, NYFA Board of Director files, and administrative/human resources information.
Historical Note
The New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA) was founded in 1971 in New York City by a group of artists who were part of the New York State Department of Cultural Affairs (NYSCA). Their goal was to create an organization that would provide artists like themselves with resources guidance and funding for their art projects that NYSCA could not provide directly. NYFA grew over the decades to become one of the leading organizations providing grants and services in New York City, New York State, and in the country. NYFA's programs are dedicated to providing guidance and support for artists and smaller arts organizations seeking city, state, and federal organization funding.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the New York Foundation for the Arts in January 2018; the accession number associated with this gift is 2018.025. An accretion to this collection was received in March 2018; the accession number associated with this gift is 2018.031.
Accruals
Further accretions to this collection are expected.
Scope and Contents
The New York Foundation for the Arts Records consists of the organization's materials for close to 50 years. The materials highlight the organization's mission to fulfill its vision in empowering emerging artists and arts organizations across all creative disciplines. The collection begins with administrative materials under Human Resources that detail committee meetings and retreats, employee handbooks and position descriptions, and office space contracts for other organization's sharing work space with NYFA. Board materials include agenda packets with meeting minutes, memorandum, and executive reports written by Ted Berger. Ted Berger's paper collection during his stint as Executive Director for NYFA is also included along with the Board's collection. The Development department's documents provide marketing materials for the annual fund, as well as NYSCA reports, and correspondence. The Finance department contributes its annual financial reports in generated in documenting the organization's yearly budget and loss, payroll, and tax returns. The Communications department adds to the mix of documents with outreach materials such as general brochures, publications, and original printed materials in support of NYFA programs made available to artists and arts organizations. A bulk of NYFA's records consist of grant applications and materials submitted by artists and arts organizations for opportunities that support the development of artists fellowships, individual and organizational art projects, arts in education implementation initiatives, and disaster relief and wage subsidy programs for events like 9/11 and Hurricane Sandy. These grant applications were also submitted to NYFA for opportunities in technology implementation by artists and arts organizations and artists' grants and cultural mission trips in Israel.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight series, some of which are further arranged into subseries:
Series I. Administrative and Human Resources
Series II. Board
Series III. Development
Subseries III.A. General
Subseries III.B. Events
Subseries III.C. Fundraiser Files
Series IV. Finance
Series V. Communications/Marketing
Series VI. Fellowship Program
Subseries VI.A. General Files
Subseries VI.B. Individual Fellow Files
Series VII. Fiscal Sponsorship
Subseries VII.A. General
Subseries VII.B. Emerging Organizations
Subseries VII.C. Artists' Projects
Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs
Subseries VIII.A. Arts in Education (AIE)
Subseries VIII.B. Artists in Residence (AIR)
Subseries VIII.C. Special Opportunity Stipend (SOS)
Subseries VIII.D. Building Up Infrastructure Levels for Dance (BUILD)
Subseries VIII.E. Community Assets
Subseries VIII.F. Disaster Relief-Related Programs
Subseries VIII.G. Cultural Blueprint for NYC
Subseries VIII.H. Felissimo
Subseries VIII.I. New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commission
Subseries VIII.J. Arts and Technology
Correspondence.; Application forms; Photographs.; Slides (photographs); Minutes (administrative records); Memorandums.; Promotional materials; Press releases.; Financial records; Architectural drawings (visual works); blueprints (reprographic copies); Printed ephemera.; Clippings (information artifacts); Art and society.; Performing arts sponsorship; Installations (Art) -- United States.; Art, Modern -- 20th century; Art, Modern -- 21st century; Art and dance; Artists and theater; Performing arts -- United States.; Community arts projects -- United States.; Art, American -- 20th century; Art, American -- 21st century; Berger, Ted; Dannenberg, Penelope; Duggan, Kevin; McCaslin, Greg; Royce, Michael; Terry, David.; Rupert, Mary Six; National Endowment for the Arts; National Campaign for Freedom of Expression (U.S.); New York State Council on the Arts; New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commission; O'Grady Foundation; Rockefeller Foundation
- Series VII. Fiscal Sponsorship, 1971-2011; 52 linear feet in 52 record cartons
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged into three subseries as follows:
  Subseries A. General Files
  Subseries B. Emerging Organizations
  Subseries C. Artists' Projects
  Scope and Contents
  This subseries consists of materials created and collected by NYFA documenting the organization's Fiscal Sponsorship program from the 1970s through the early 2000s. Materials in this subseries include internal correspondence, memoranda, financial records, applications and registration forms, and research materials concerning the economic climate of the early 2000s. Individual applications consist of organization descriptions; project narrative proposals; proposed budgets; and documentation of proposed timelines, audiences, promotional plans, and fundraising strategies. Materials in this series document the methods by which NYFA provides resources to support working artists and arts organizations, and the larger context of non-profit programming to foster artistic and creative projects. The series also demonstrates the breadth of artistic projects supported through the program, including visual arts, theater, dance, film, performance art, literature, and inter-disciplinary works.
  - Subseries A. General, 1971-2009; 2 linear feet in 2 record cartons
    This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were created and maintained.
    This subseries consists of materials created and collected by NYFA documenting the organization's Fiscal Sponsorship program from the 1970s through the early 2000s. Materials in this subseries include internal correspondence, memoranda, financial records, applications and registration forms, and research materials concerning the economic climate of the early 2000s. This subseries documents the administrative aspects of the the sponsorship process, the methods by which NYFA provides resources and organizational infrastructure to support working artists and arts organizations, and the larger context of non-profit programming to foster artistic and creative projects.
    - General Files, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Registration Forms, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-2000 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Stock Certificates of Agristar, General Ledger Reports, Check Status, Invoices, 2008 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Memorandums, Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - "Exhibition Checklist", 2006 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Recession Strategies, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Memos, 2009 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Cultural Data Project, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Memorandum, etc., 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia Seminar, 2008 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Data Control Card Applications, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Registration Forms, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Registration Forms, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Registration Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Registration Forms, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Registration Forms, 1990-2000 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Registration Forms, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence and Cycle Application Reviews, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Cycle Application Reviews, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - General Files, 1986-2005 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Requirements for Benefits and Fund Raising Materials, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Incorporation Information, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Program Mission Statement, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - "Strategy and High Level Action Plan", 2007 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Fiscally Sponsored Projects List, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Artists Project Lists, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Mission Statement, General (Blank) Program Forms, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - NYFA Founding Documents, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - NYFA By-Laws, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Grant Proposal Writing Material, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - NYFA Dealing with Economic Downturn Material, 2007-2009 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - NYFA Dealing with Financial Downturn Material, 2007-2009 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Furlow Responses, 2009 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - NYFA Plans to Deal with Economic Downturn, 2007-2009 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Proposal Writing Seminar Series Program, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Photographs Promotional Material, Postcards, 1980-2000 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Promotional Materials From Artists/Organizations, 1990-2000 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Promotional Materials From Artists/Organizations, 1990-2000 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Promotional Material, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Artists Promotional Materials, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - General Files, 1971-2016 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Promotional Materials, Posters, Newspaper Articles, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - NYSCA Final Report Certifications, 2009 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - General Files, Appplication Materials, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Unfinished Project Applications, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - General Files, Trust for Material Understanding, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Cycle Applications, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - NYICC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - NYICC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - NYICC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - NYICC Grant Application Project Name: Celebrate Brooklyn! Performing Arts Festival, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - NYICC Grant Application (Blank), 2002 (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - NYICC Correspondence: Minister Counselor Administrative Affairs Letter, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - NYICCC Correspondence: Herzliya Museum, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - NYICCC Grant Application: North American Jewish Choral Festival, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - NYICCC Press List Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - NYICCC Correspondence Art in General, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - NYICCC Program Preliminary Application, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - NYICCC Contact Sheet, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - NYICCC Correspondence NYSCA's List of Museums in NYS, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - NYICCC Presenters List, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - NYICCC Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - NYICCC Chairman's Report, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - NYICCC Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - NYICCC Agendas, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - Faxes to French Institute Alliance Francaise, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - NYICCC FY 02 Budget Ledger, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - NYICCC Chairman's Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - NyICCC Administration, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - NYICCC Letter of Agreement with ESDC, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - NYICCC Disbursements, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - NYICCC Old Budget Information, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 53)
    - NYICCC Funding Balance Sheet, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 54)
  - Subseries B. Emerging Organizations, 1980-2008; 14 linear feet in 14 record cartons
    This series has been arranged alphabetically by organization name.
    This subseries contains applications to NYFA's Fiscal Sponsorship program that are categorized as Emerging Organizations, which must be incorporated as a nonprofit on the state level. Applications consist of organization descriptions; project narrative proposals; proposed budgets; and documentation of proposed timelines, audiences, promotional plans, and fundraising strategies. This subseries also includes correspondence, annual progress reports, and promotional materials to advertise specific programming. Materials in this subseries document the individual organizations associated with the fiscal sponsorship program, as well as the breadth of artistic projects supported through it, including visual arts, theater, dance, film, performance art, literature, and inter-disciplinary works.
    - Ivan C. Alicia, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Arts in Education, 1995-1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Arts Economic Fund, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - ArtsWire, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - ArtsWire, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Planning Commission Budgets, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Embry Art Consulting, 1997-2000 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Commission of the NYC Department of Cultural Affairs, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Aviva Players, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Aviva Players, 1980-1990 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Beaver Group, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Film Networks, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - A-1 Collaborators, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Internship Program, Office of the Mayor of NYC, 1996-1998 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Ballad Theatre, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Ballad Theatre, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Bandwagon Musicals, 1984-1987 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Bandwagon of Vintage Musicals, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Billboard Museum, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Crosstown Ensemble, 1994-1997 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Cenway and Pratt, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - CCOSI, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - CCOSI, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - CCOSI, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Dance Heritage Coalition, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - The Design Trust For Public Space, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Education Project, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Education Project, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Fabrics of Faith, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - AmDat, Inc., 2004 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - NY Department of Cultural Affairs, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Bank Line of Credit Increase, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - The Penny Bridge Players, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - The Cultural Coalition of Staten Island, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Blackberry Productions, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Ninth Street Theater, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files (NYFA), 1990 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, 1994-1997 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, Berlin Film Festival, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, 1980-1990 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Drum Songs, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, NYFA/NY Department of Cultural Affairs, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Sponsorship General Files, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Salon 300, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Film Office, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Hamptons Shakespeare Festival, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Hamptons Shakespeare Festival, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - N40 NYC Arts-In-Education Theatre, 1998-1999 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Labryinth, Inc., L-21, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Labryinth, Inc., L-21, 1997-1999 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Labryinth, Inc., L-21, 1996-1998 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Emerging Organizations, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Weblab/Dig., 2000 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Weblab, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Weblab, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Weblab, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Weblab, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Bridge Players, Incl, 1995-1999 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Playwrights of New York, 1990-2000 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Blackboard/NYFA General, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Drum Songs Productions, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - NYFA General Program Information, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - NYFA General/NEA Audit, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - One Step Forward, NYFA General, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - One Foot Forward, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 36)
    - Six Ways to Do It Right, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Silk, Adler and Calvin, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence between NYFA and Lawyers, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - List of Sponsored Organizations, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Drafts, Agreements, Legal Departments, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Question for Jerome, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Sponsor Meeting Notes, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Kevin Duggan, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence between Jerome Caulfield and Kevin Duggan, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - The Rosen Fund for New York City, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Blackberry Productions, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - NYFA Sponsored Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Integral Projects Meetings, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Integral Projects, Elaine's Research, 1991-1996 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Integral Projectsion, Evaluation Form, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Integral Projects, Review Forms, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Bozart Mountain Jade Films, 1989-1990 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Management Services Agreements, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Management Agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Media Network, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Penny Legal Documents, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Weblab, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Grants given in 2005 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Fred Gates Design Lease Agreement, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - General Files, Booklets, Sponsored Entities, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Foundation Research, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - The Tides Foundation, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Drafts, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Plans, Structuring, other General Sponsorship Program Material, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Communications, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Drafts, Correspondence, Plans, Charts, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Memos, Reports, Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, Drafts, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - Program Materials, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 34)
    - Job Descriptions and Definitions, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 35)
    - Memos, Policy and Procedure Writings, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 36)
    - Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, General Program Material, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 37)
    - List of Organizations and Tax Exempt Status, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 38)
    - Wind Artists Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 84, Folder 39)
    - Wind Artists Foundation, 1980-1992 (Box 84, Folder 40)
    - Zone West Theatre, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 41)
    - Zone West Theatre, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 42)
    - The Window Project, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 43)
    - The Window Project, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 44)
    - Wind Artists Foundation, 1983-1993 (Box 84, Folder 45)
    - New York Woodwind Quintet, 1990-1993 (Box 84, Folder 46)
    - Testing the Limits, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 47)
    - Wind Artists Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 84, Folder 48)
    - Wind Artists Foundation, 1983-1993 (Box 84, Folder 49)
    - Precious Cargo/The Garner Documentary Group, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - NYFA Technology Plan, 1996-1999 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Program Documents (General), 1990 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - ArtsWire, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - ArtsWire, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - General Files, Sponsor Projects Reconciliations, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - General Files, Payment Receipts, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - New York City Choral Music Initiative, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - NEA Allocation, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - General Files, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Talking Drum, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - THAT WAS FAST, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - THAT WAS FAST, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - THAT WAS FAST/Richard James Allen and Karen Pearlman, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - THAT WAS FAST, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - The Education Project, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Lannan, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Question of Equarity, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Completed Application Files, Polaris North, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Polaris North, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Design Arts, NEA Grants Application Application Material, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Art Commission of the City of New York, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Art Commission of the City of New York, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Art Commission of the City of New York, 1970-1980 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Big Apple Highway Beautification Project, Landscape Improvement Project Contact, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Big Apple Highway Beautification Project, Landscape Improvement Project Contact, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Renaissance Motion Pictures, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - NEA Applications, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - Williams, Nik, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Stuart, 1989-1993 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Kay, 2000-2004 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - The B-Team, Inc., 1997-2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - The coOPERAtive, 1998-2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Complexions, Inc., 2000-2006 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Complexions, Inc., 2000-2006 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - The coOPERAtive, 1998-2003 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - free103point9, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - The Great American Book Project, 2001-2003 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - International Photography Institute, 2001-2003 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - International Photography Institute, 2001-2003 (Box 86, Folder 12)